SUMMARY

An IT specialist who is experienced in multinational projects is willing to maximize excellent abilities and to deliver a high professional attitude in order to be a strong asset to the property



• NAME : (Karen) Eunjou Kim

ADDRESS: Schoenhofstr.10, 60487, Frankfurt, Germany

MOBILE: +4915778310484
 EMAIL: kkarenej@gmail.com
 DATE OF BIRTH: 29 June 1987
 NATIONALITY: Republic of Korea

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Language : Java (JEE6, 7), Javascript (Angular JS1), SQL, iBM CL

• Internet Technology Experience: Extensive experience with web service, servlets / JSP, XML and XSL, Client-server architecture / XHTML, HTML, CSS, iBATIS Framework

System: UNIX (Linux, Solaris), Windows
Database: IBM DB2, JDBC, ODBC, MySQL

EXPERIENCE

HYUNDAI MOBIS EUROPE (FRANKFURT, GERMANY)

02 / 2014 - Present

SENIOR ADVISOR IT SPECIALIST

Responsible for web based application (RIA) systems and projects for all Hyundai/Kia Motors subsidiaries

- Implement international projects creating operational mature solutions
 - : ERP system for manufacturing, sales, logistics, personnel, and accounting and external business process information for customers and suppliers to provide the optimal business management environment. Deploy web based PDA system for 8 European warehouses
- Front-end and Back-end Java, JSP, Javascript, XML development to support new business processes in designated locations: including e-commerce set-up with data transfer via web service (SOAP), implementing SSO, improve security modules including SQL injection prevention, proficient in manipulating properties and methods of document objects and modifying attributes and values via the DOM
- Translate business requirements into web analytical technical documentation
- Result reporting and accountability to the management, improve and monitor performance of IT operations

 query optimization, web server maintenance, DW server monitoring, trouble shooting JavaScript code using tools such as FireBug, Fiddler
- Create and maintain user manuals, provide user training on client applications
- Support includes development of user applications, bug fixes, modification/enhancements to existing functions, testing, system documentation, and ad-hoc data gathering/queries

HYUNDAI MOBIS EUROPE (FRANKFURT, GERMANY)

05 / 2012 - 01 / 2014

ONLINE MARKETING SPECIALIST

Project coordinator on cooperative marketing channel

- Assist project managers in drafting and selection of external service providers, issuance of project proposals, RFP's, tenders, budgets, cash flows and preliminary schedules
- Track the progress and quality of work being performed by design disciplines/trades
- Effectively and accurately communicate relevant project information to the client and project team
- Highly involved in directing UX/UI design based on user behavior analysis and planning CMS for customers
- Support online marketing projects throughout social networking site and monitor on Google analytics
- Increase user satisfaction by contributing to and supporting the development, conduct and analysis of user surveys

KAREN EUNJOU KIM

kkarenej@gmailcom +4915778310484

HONEYWELL KOREA (SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA)

02/2011-07/2011

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERNSHIP

- Testing software modules of gas detecting system
- Simulation and modeling on Linux testing environment
- Assistance of documenting software architecture blueprints

ORACLE INDIA (BANGALORE, INDIA)

03 / 2010 - 12 / 2010

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

- Hands-on practices of Oracle database
- Technical translation / interpretation within the team
- Research on real-time data handling system
- End user training and reports work on document composition

EDUCATION

BOSTON UNIVERSITY - Boston, Messachusettes, US

Master of Science (Msc), Computer Information Systems (Distance learning)

05/2016 – Present 02/2007- 08/2012

SUNGKONGHOE UNIVERSITY - Seoul, S.Korea

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Computer Science and Communication (GPA 3.8/4.0)

- Web programming
- Object-oriented programming
- System architecture
- Embedded system programming
- Mobile programming (Android)
- Network and communication theory

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

KOREAN : Native

JAPANESE: Full professional proficiency
 ENGLISH: Full Professional Proficiency
 GERMAN: Limited Working Proficiency (B1)

• FRENCH : Elementary Proficiency (A2)